

KEANUE DAX TEAÑO



+639-363866706



keanuedax@gmail.com



https://github.com/Daxu010



Cabangcalan 1, Bulacao Cebu

ABOUT ME

A Computer Engineering graduate with the interest of Designing and Creating artforms in the field of Lay-Outing, Video/Photo Editing and UX/UI Design. I will bring off the knowledge already gained to achieve career growth and experience.

SKILLS

- Management Skills
- Communication skills
- Innovation skills
- Critical Thinking
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- · Web Design
- Photo & Video Editing

TRAININGS AND SEMINARS

- Basic Web Designing
- Robotics Training Workshop
- Cisco Introduction Packet Tracer
- Data Structural and **Analytics Analysis**
- Machine Learning
- PSITE7

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering Cebu Institute of Technology-University

2018-Present

N. Bacalso Ave., Cebu City

Senior High School

Cebu Institute of Technology-University

2016-2018

N. Bacalso Ave., Cebu City

Science. Technology, Mathematics (STEM)

Engineering and

EXPERIENCES

Sprobe Inc.

June 2022 - August 2022

The Technologian

2021 - 2022

2020 - 2021

The Technologian

Internship

Cebu Business Park

Arts & Graphics Editor

Cebu Institute of Technology -University | Student Publication

Layout Design Editor

Cebu Institute of Technology -University | Student Publication

The Technologian Student Press Lavout Artist

2019 - 2020

Cebu Institute of Technology -University | Student Publication

Cebu Institute of Technology - University

2018 - 2019

2015 - 2019

Non - Academic Scholar Front Desk | Safety & Security Office

Cebu Institute of Technology

- University

WFH

Bulacao, Cebu

PORTFOLIO

Freelance Layout Artist

- EVote System
- CCT | Contactless Covid Tracer
- TeknoyEMS
- GarPo